[
    {
        "question": "2 - 1",
        "answer": "1",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 3",
        "answer": "2",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 4",
        "answer": "4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 6",
        "answer": "3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 2",
        "answer": "7",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 3",
        "answer": "5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 1",
        "answer": "9",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 4",
        "answer": "6",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 2",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 1",
        "answer": "5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 2",
        "answer": "2",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 3",
        "answer": "3",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 6",
        "answer": "4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 1",
        "answer": "4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 5",
        "answer": "1",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 1",
        "answer": "7",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 7",
        "answer": "1",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 3",
        "answer": "1",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 6",
        "answer": "2",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 4",
        "answer": "2",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]
